Ernest K.K Amankwah

Front-end Developer

Profile

I am a developer with fluent skills in front-end web development, and some additional programming experience in React.js, Matlab, java, and few frameworks. My personal experience has made me an efficient problem solver. My years in school have given me the exposure to basic concepts relating Computer Science. I have attained knowledge in software development; thus, Front end development. I am ready to learn and expand my exposure and experience, when given the right opportunities.

Professional Experience

University of Energy and Natural resources, Software developer

11/2023 - present | SUNYANI, Ghana

Working as a junior software developer with the universities IT directorate in developing and monitoring the academic tracker to improve its efficiency.

Newmont Ghana Gold, Technician

09/2021 - 12/2021 | Sunyani, Ghana

Worked as an intern with ritetech ventures, responsible for the installation of wireless AP's, mounting and configuration of radios, trouble shooting, running and termination of fibre and ethernet cables.

Certificates

React Basics meta course (Issued by coursera)

JavaScript meta course (Issued by coursera)

Education

Bsc. Computer Engineering,

UNIVERSITY OF ENERGY AND NATURAL RESOURCES

2019 - present | Sunyani, Ghana

Senior High School, (Opoku Ware School)

2016 - 2019 | kumasi, Ghana

Skills

Languages

JavaScript, Html 5, CSS 3

Others

Command line, Package managers, Git and Github,

Technologies

React.js

Projects

Portfolio site 🛮